Roman Siuma

Unity Game Developer

+3800956083297

• Lvivska, Ukraine

Profile

Hi, my name is Roman, and I've been making video games for the past 5 years. After graduating the university, I worked as an intern in a game company for about a year, and I have acquired the valuable experience in implementing core game mechanics, and optimizing game performance.

I genuinely enjoy making games and working with others who share my interests. Now I am working as a freelancer and hope to work and learn from everyone regarding game development.

Professional Experience

Game Developer, Self Employed

August 2022 - May 2023

- Networking development/support.
- Fixed bugs during development and in production.
- Provided support to the teams who re-use the developed technologies.
- Analyzed existing code and propose efficient solutions.
- Cooperate with designers, programmers and testers to bring suggestions from an idea to released future.
- Interacted with clients to determine project's technical requirements and needs.
- Implement new game features and services in close partnership with the content team of the project and with respect for the player's comfort and game's performance

Unity Game Developer, Gameloft, Internship

July 2021 – July 2022 | Kharkiv, Kharkiv Oblast, Ukraine

- Developed and implemented gameplay mechanics, systems, and features using Unity and C#
- Collaborated with designers and artists to bring game concepts to life
- Optimized game performance and implement efficient coding practices
- Debug and resolved technical issues and bugs
- Participated in code reviews to maintain code quality and ensure best practices
- Worked with team leads to help make architectural decisions for the betterment of current and future projects
- Contributed to the planning of tasks for each sprint
- Developed better and more efficient workflows and helped implement them for team

Education

Bachelor's Degree / Computer Science, Sumy State University January 2017 – January 2021 | Sumy Oblast, Ukraine